<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lightning Talk</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome! We are going to take a quick view at the UI components that make up Android apps.</string>
    <string name="what_is_android">What is Android?</string>
    <string name="android_description">-Android is an open-source operating system that is based in Linux\n-Though the open-source nature of Android, the most widely used version is maintained by Google\n-It is the most widely used mobile operating system</string>
    <string name="programming_languages">Programming Languages?</string>
    <string name="language_descriptions">-Java was the original language used\n-Kotlin is now the preferred language by Google, however Java is still used</string>
    <string name="fun_fact">Fun Fact!</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_description">-All major updates are named after desserts and in alphabetical order\n-This version\'s name is Tiramisu!</string>
    <string name="lightning_talk">Android Lightning Talk!</string>
    <string name="next">Next!</string>
    <string name="xml">XML</string>
    <string name="what_is_xml">What is XML?</string>
    <string name="xml_description">-XML stands for extensible markup language\n-Used for storing data</string>
    <string name="how_is_it_used_in_android">How is it used in Android?</string>
    <string name="used_in_android_description">-Used to create content on Android Activities\n-Stores information such as color, strings, and images to be called\n-Best practice is to save all editable information into its own XML file within the resources\n-Each resource has its own name and description</string>
    <string name="what_are_activities">What are activities?</string>
    <string name="activities_quick_description">-We are in one right now!\n-Refers to the screen layouts (pages)\n-We will move on to the next screen to dive into Activities a bit more</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="switch_on">Switch is on</string>
    <string name="add_item">Add Item</string>
    <string name="delete_item">Delete Item</string>
    <string name="toast">Toast!</string>
    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="tell_activites">How do we tell activities what to do?</string>
    <string name="oncreate_details">-Each XML file can be associated with a class\n-Instead of a Main function, there is the onCreate function\n-When an activity loads or changes, the onCreaate is called\n-Listeners can be placed here or outside if the task is more specific</string>
    <string name="what_are_listeners">What are Listeners?</string>
    <string name="listener_desc">-Listeners tell components within activities what they do when interacted with\n-Buttons, switches, spinners can all get listeners</string>
    <string name="android_manifest">Android Manifest</string>
    <string name="what_is_the_android_manifest">What is the Android Manifest?</string>
    <string name="manifest_items">-Contains important information about the application contents\n-Sets a range of information from labels at the top of the screen to the target API\n-Without the Manifest, your app will not function</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="pressed">Button pressed!</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_list">
        <item>TextView</item>
        <item>Button</item>
        <item>Switch</item>
        <item>Spinner</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>